{
    "answerPrefix": "What is..",
    "categories": [
        {
            "title": "tv in xxxx",
            "description": "Shows which got aired in 2013",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "This anime features kirito.",
                    "answer": [ "Sword Art Online" ],
                    "points": 100
                },
                {
                    "question": "This DC animated tv show featuring sidekicks received a reboot in xxxx.",
                    "answer": [
                        "Teen Titans",
                        "Teen Titans GO",
                        "Teen Titans GO!"
                    ],
                    "points": 200
                },
                {
                    "question": "This crime drama series, which took place in albuquerque, new mexico",
                    "answer": [ "breaking bad" ],
                    "points": 300
                },
                {
                    "question": "This comedic docu-reality show, which features a business school graduate and his elaborate schemes.",
                    "answer": [ "Nathan for you" ],
                    "points": 400
                },
                {
                    "question": "This short-lived comedy series, created by bo burnham.",
                    "answer": [ "Zach Stone" ],
                    "points": 500
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Category",
            "description": "Shows which got aired in 2013",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "This anime features kirito.",
                    "answer": [ "Sword Art Online" ],
                    "points": 100
                },
                {
                    "question": "This DC animated tv show featuring sidekicks received a reboot in xxxx.",
                    "answer": [
                        "Teen Titans",
                        "Teen Titans GO",
                        "Teen Titans GO!"
                    ],
                    "points": 200
                },
                {
                    "question": "This crime drama series, which took place in albuquerque, new mexico",
                    "answer": [ "breaking bad" ],
                    "points": 300
                },
                {
                    "question": "This comedic docu-reality show, which features a business school graduate and his elaborate schemes.",
                    "answer": [ "Nathan for you" ],
                    "points": 400
                },
                {
                    "question": "This short-lived comedy series, created by bo burnham.",
                    "answer": [ "Zach Stone" ],
                    "points": 500
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Category",
            "description": "Shows which got aired in 2013",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "This anime features kirito.",
                    "answer": [ "Sword Art Online" ],
                    "points": 100
                },
                {
                    "question": "This DC animated tv show featuring sidekicks received a reboot in xxxx.",
                    "answer": [
                        "Teen Titans",
                        "Teen Titans GO",
                        "Teen Titans GO!"
                    ],
                    "points": 200
                },
                {
                    "question": "This crime drama series, which took place in albuquerque, new mexico",
                    "answer": [ "breaking bad" ],
                    "points": 300
                },
                {
                    "question": "This comedic docu-reality show, which features a business school graduate and his elaborate schemes.",
                    "answer": [ "Nathan for you" ],
                    "points": 400
                },
                {
                    "question": "This short-lived comedy series, created by bo burnham.",
                    "answer": [ "Zach Stone" ],
                    "points": 500
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Category",
            "description": "Shows which got aired in 2013",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "This anime features kirito.",
                    "answer": [ "Sword Art Online" ],
                    "points": 100
                },
                {
                    "question": "This DC animated tv show featuring sidekicks received a reboot in xxxx.",
                    "answer": [
                        "Teen Titans",
                        "Teen Titans GO",
                        "Teen Titans GO!"
                    ],
                    "points": 200
                },
                {
                    "question": "This crime drama series, which took place in albuquerque, new mexico",
                    "answer": [ "breaking bad" ],
                    "points": 300
                },
                {
                    "question": "This comedic docu-reality show, which features a business school graduate and his elaborate schemes.",
                    "answer": [ "Nathan for you" ],
                    "points": 400
                },
                {
                    "question": "This short-lived comedy series, created by bo burnham.",
                    "answer": [ "Zach Stone" ],
                    "points": 500
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Category",
            "description": "Shows which got aired in 2013",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "This anime features kirito.",
                    "answer": [ "Sword Art Online" ],
                    "points": 100
                },
                {
                    "question": "This DC animated tv show featuring sidekicks received a reboot in xxxx.",
                    "answer": [
                        "Teen Titans",
                        "Teen Titans GO",
                        "Teen Titans GO!"
                    ],
                    "points": 200
                },
                {
                    "question": "This crime drama series, which took place in albuquerque, new mexico",
                    "answer": [ "breaking bad" ],
                    "points": 300
                },
                {
                    "question": "This comedic docu-reality show, which features a business school graduate and his elaborate schemes.",
                    "answer": [ "Nathan for you" ],
                    "points": 400
                },
                {
                    "question": "This short-lived comedy series, created by bo burnham.",
                    "answer": [ "Zach Stone" ],
                    "points": 500
                }
            ]
        }
    ]

}